# Carla Conradie

**Product Designer** 

London, UK

+447535991636

in LinkedIn profile

Portfolio website

#### **About**

Product designer with a background in delivering visual effects work for Hollywood film productions. Extensive experience taking projects from brief to launch, understanding and executing on client needs, collaborating with cross-functional teams in international contexts, and finding the right solutions to creative and technical problems.

# **Professional Experience**

#### **Associate VFX Producer, Untold Studios**

February 2024 - present, London

Lead a team in delivering VFX work for animated feature film, overseeing creative presentations and iterative feedback loop with clients at Paramount Pictures. Manage resourcing and development of internal team as well as client priorities. Sit on leadership committee implementing changes to production tools and establishing best practices across the studio.

#### Associate VFX Producer, One of Us

March 2022 - February 2024, Paris/London

Spearheaded overhaul of studio's primary production tool, ShotGrid, collaborating with technology teams to improve UX/ UI of database and optimise workflows. Enhanced productivity and client satisfaction for two largest and most complex projects to date, both Netflix feature films.

#### VFX Line Producer, Framestore

October 2019 - March 2022, London

Built and managed production schedule for various VFX features, translating technical requirements and budgetary restrictions into daily feedback process. Oversaw execution of delivery targets and design reviews to meet creative vision of clients at A24, Warner Bros, and Netflix/StudioCanal.

# **Projects**

# **UX/UI Designer, Village Childcare App**

Career Foundry project case study, April 2024

Designed an app enabling families to connect for childcare needs. Conducted user research, built interactive prototypes with Figma, and responded to usability test results to produce high fidelity mockups meeting both iOS and Android guidelines.

#### Education

### **Career Foundry**

2023-2024, London

Certificate in UI Design with a specialisation in Frontend Development for Designers

#### McGill University/Sciences Po

2011-2015, Montréal/Paris

B.A. Art History + Political Science with 12 month bilingual exchange program

## Volunteer Experience

#### Youth Mentor, Baytree Centre

September 2018 - May 2022, London

Met weekly with two young girls to set and achieve personal and academic goals and participate in character education workshops to develop qualities for success

### Skills Tools

User Research Figma **User Personas** Basic HTML/CSS Wireframing GitHub Google Suite Prototyping MS Office Suite **UI** Design Slack Mockups **Usability Testing JIRA** Project Management ShotGrid Client Relations Leadership/Mentorship

# Languages

English (fluent)
French (fluent)
Afrikaans (fluent)
Spanish (intermediate)
Brazilian Portuguese (elementary)

Communication/Team Building

Data Visualisation/Forecasting